I'm coming back to you
And I hope you don't mind that I'm wasting your time
I know you want me too
Even though you're not mine
You got that look in your eyes
Come on tell me where you at
When you're back
I won't keep you up
Take a nap
A little gasoline and a match
You just like it better when it's cold
This ain't what you want
This is what you need
Wake up in the morning
Know just what ya need need need need
I'm coming back to you
So I really hope that you don't mind
I know you want me too
Even though you're not mine
You got that look in your eyes
Can you remember when I crossed it
Put the sweat up in this
Like a mosh pit
Think I'm done up in this
Don't you stop me
Don't wanna see you throw a fit
You just like it better when it's cold